Hi, guys. One second. Invite a joker over.
I don't know if you can make it, but here we go, guys.
Hi, Lace. With a quick little introduction.
Hey, oh, hey, joker. What's up? Thanks for coming over.
Joker, I'll mod you in a second.
You're just as, you know, you're kind of like my,
one of my people that brought me into this world.
Okay, I got it. Let me see
Love you Joker. This is it. I'll just play one quick video pre-muffy. I'm up here. Okay
Midnight, you want to get timed out midnight? You're about to get timed out
You want it midnight
Thank you, Ms. Liz. I love you, too. Yeah, I just play one quick video. It's only two and a half minutes
Okay, there's just like kind of like my recruitment quote recruitment video
You didn't find us
We found you
Sorry about the weird feeling in your spine, that's normal
Welcome to the cold where the Wi-Fi's curse and the truth gets kidnapped
Gently then rehearse where the shadows talk back and the terror throws shade and the guests on the panel look fresh from a
Side quest rate. We got chaos in the challenge wisdom in the dark a trope reward on the door
Still kidding but not far. If you're looking for a meaning, baby, right on track. Just don't ask Google as a voice is whispering back
So loose in your halo
It was from on the way, but that's hide you know what
Slightly, we're not a real co, but like we're also not not we got candles lower and a membership spa
We got cosmic punch lines astrology and the algorithm chained in the back making coffee your higher self
Please log in your lower cells here to try to sneak some sins the middle self
Oh, we just showed up for fun. None of us are whole babe. That's why we're
Welcome to the cold of psyche
Where the wild feels warm and inviting
Where the truth comes out fighting biting
But damn, the lighting is exciting
Yeah, this is the cold of psyche
Where the loss feels strangely mighty
You belong here, come nightly
Where the shadows glow
And the strange fits tightly
It has begun
You know
Chicks will come back like on his own time like
It's dark outside. I don't have a flashlight like with batteries and stuff right now. I
mean
Cats will hide they'll be scared nearby
He'll come like he'll come and stuff
The only reason he wouldn't come is if something kind of bad happened and that's the only I'm worried about
But I looked at the street. I didn't see any
Charitable things. I'm afraid to look at the fucking
Stuff if he doesn't come back tonight, I'll be like tomorrow. I'll be looking on like all the websites and stuff
I'm just like trying to like
Think positively right now
Exendo
I mean I'll hide midnight tomorrow, but midnight I keep warning midnight like don't say like fucked up shit to me and
That got too personal, so
Got a little bit too personal
Like it's my fault and like, you know, I'm not doing enough
You know, I have these treats. I'm gonna shake the treats on the window. I'm gonna call for them. I
Don't want to like think the worst. Hey, I have a cult member come in
Yo, I'm a cult member cult member. Thank you, Joker or mr. Extendo
You have to say it with a W it's to extend Oh
What should we do on this stream?
It's okay, it's I know like a midnight is like kind of just always like a little bit of a troll and stuff
And it's kind of like I just like time out midnight, but it's like kind of went a little too far with the comments
It's like not like I don't have the kind of relationship where we can joke around like that. It's not a joke either
It's like something that just like hurts my heart
Joker you saw my tattoo Joker
The cat killer. I don't think I like that main
Guys Aaron if you thought you get a bad feeling for that person. I trust your intuition about it
If you don't mind helping me Hebrew sense you okay, you can you can like
Stay I guess but if you get a bad feeling
Me night is nice. She busts everyone's ball, but she's talking about my cat this missing saying oh
It's a woman with a cat Williams picture and stuff
But midnight said oh you're you're out getting cigarettes instead of looking
I don't know, but do you want to see here my tattoo
Are you wearing what are you wearing underneath that a
Pair of American flag Speedos, would you like to see them?
I'm not
Just actually make it under there
The speed is wearing so I think he's wearing an undergarment
I
I wear the speed is for like two days in a row
If I wore them three days in a row, you know the American flag
I don't want the American flag to turn brown and so I'm just kidding. That was a bad joke
But they're in the wash. They're just in the wash right now
I don't want to I don't want to sack or lives the American flag. I'm so sorry. I'm muted. Oh shit
I'm you said Joker. Don't complain. Don't pretend that you're not gay
Gay isn't what gay isn't happy. He's happy. I'm always happy. I
Mean Joker's told the story about how he woke up one night
Oh, I think he woke up one night and a guy was giving him a blow job and I said, well, what did you do?
And he said I let him finish
Well first of all, it was a sticky situation. It was it was it was it was it was okay
There's a lot of things that went into that. Okay. Yeah. Yeah, I'm sorry. I'm sorry
And I know I don't need to like take it out of context and stuff
But you did let him finish right?
Well
I was asleep at my friend's house and my friend did a bunch of bad stuff, you know, it's nasty
so I woke up and
They were doing things with their mouth
To my balls, and I was like, oh, I don't know what to do
It was a sticky situation
It was and I was like, you know some people some guys was like say oh
I put I punched them in the face and they get the fuck off me and stuff. What did you do when you when you woke up?
I went back to sleep.
Okay.
I just closed my eyes.
You found him, Jesus?
Okay.
I figured I was their practice.
You know, like for their practice,
they were trying it out, you know.
How are you doing?
Joker, can I practice on you too?
They said not funny.
I just didn't, I don't know.
It's funny to really think about it.
Yeah, Joker, I just,
it was a joke, it was a joke, it was a joke.
Um, it's fine Joker actually also was very open about his friend if your friend transitions or something like that
I don't know what's the friends name is like RG kind of had a friend and he started wearing more women's wigs
And women's clothes
And he used to steal women's clothes so that he could wear them
I didn't know this until later on that he would steal the females clothes of females
So we'd hang out with and then he'd wear them
And then what happened with him?
He turned into a woman and then what do you what do you do with him, Joanie?
I don't know. He just started wearing wigs and started dressing up as a woman.
You didn't have a threesome or something? Was there a threesome involved?
No, there was not. There was not.
Okay, never mind. Never mind. I went to... Oh, I said it's also...
Yeah, I just let them go their own way and do what they do. I didn't have, like, any big issue with it.
You said, you can go your own way.
They said, am I wearing fishnets? Am I wearing fishnets?
Can I see? I want to see.
I'm wearing shorts.
I work shorts, dude. How would I wear fishnets, dude?
Well, I
Would if you asked me to wear them I'd wear them for you your chat is
I know my chat is my chat is insane
No, someone's who's calling me a Goyam. Someone's calling me a Goyam
That's an insane guy with that. So what are you wearing fishnets? Like are you wearing fishnets right now?
If you want me to all I can wear them
Would you like me to wear them?
Would you wear them for the stream? No, I wear them for you. If you want me to wear my stream I'll warm on stream
Dude, I got to get a new phone
I dropped my phone on the ground and now my phone sounds like I can't like it just sounds all multiple
Shit, how's muffy by the way?
I call him old boy now. Oh boy. I thought I was a girl. I thought I was a woman dog
But Joker has a boy dog in his name is muffin. His name is muffin. And what is it Prince?
Cavalier or a print Charles Cavalier Charles spaniel a
Prince Charles Cavalier spaniel and he's he's an adorable dog. He's a very you know, he's a very
Looks like a little pampered dog and stuff like it looks like a royalty actually and Joker. What's the game?
Yeah
You're playing it. You're piecing in the sink. I do that sometimes it's kind of like you play chivalry to
chivalry shoe
I pee in the sink sometimes. I'm most hated. Well, I you're playing this game tonight
It was like I don't know what was the scenery check Republic or something like that like I've been to check Republic
I look like Europe somewhere
that's just like some european setting and like some like uh...
some
can i play with you
if i get it
yeah are you also i what can i join your uh... give a gt a five or six gang
not yet
do you want to start one?
yeah i have to get the game though i don't have to get the game
I have GTA 5. I think I mean it's on sale usually for like 10 bucks and stuff
And then they had the GT online and stuff, but then you can start a gang Danny used to love
Playing GTA 5 and like I was like can I join your game? You know what's funny about Danny though?
He was wearing I said can I buy your wife beater? And you know what he said?
What he said wife? He's called a white beater. I
Like no, they're called wife beaters Danny
He said they are I was like Danny. They're called a wife 100%. They're called wife beaters not called white beaters
He thought
Up until he was 41 years old. I told him like a few weeks before and unfortunately passed away. They're called
Wife beaters and he said white beater white that they're called white beaters
Yeah, I think it's just kind of just one of those charming things about him like that, you know
He is this week. I I don't know if you ever see you ever see Danny Joker or no
Yeah, you never saw him like I do have like a we saw the video I played the video for you, right where he's like
You know, he did these like shots of alcohol. He saw that one, right? Do you see him when he looks like what do you die?
He got shot three times in the chest of the gas. Oh, he's the guy that was screaming you were telling me about
Yeah, not seen the video of him like was it live
Well, no, well, I'm not like on he was live streaming and stuff when it happened like but he was at a local gas station and
He make the news
Yes, and you can hear the gunshots and stuff don't play the news story
There's a new story. Oh shit. Yeah, I'll play it real quick. Hold on. I'll find it real quick. I
Didn't know this. I mean, I remember you vaguely telling me a vaguely remember
Yeah, it's so he was one of my pendant. It is a cross is a cross
It keeps me from
all these haters
stew
I don't know. Okay, so I'm gonna say Danny stranger on
I'm gonna say Danny stranger because it's but it says there's like a big there's like a identification of a victim of the gas station
He was killed at a Costco. I don't know this guy. I don't doesn't I know his last name and stuff
Let me see if I Danny stranger comes up. Oh
Yeah, and so he also did the one ship challenge and stuff
You know all say is that I sense like there was like something weird
Going on like because he was like on and when I click
Let me see if I can find the news story though, or if I can't find I'm first
I'll show his video if I can't find the news story right away. I'll find I'll look for the news story, but
Okay, I don't see it right away, but I will show you
The the video I made what he was welcome to my chat he did a shot
Yeah, welcome to joke and and and make sure you
I'm not on my phone. So I feel as I have a broken phone. So I don't
think it's so but a few months before he passed away, I did write a song for him because okay, so
I'll tell this story last year, you know, Piranha, I'm okay. He I was in his chat and I thought hey,
this guy's cute and then
But he banned me from his chat right away
because I used him an emoji
and he thought I was hitting on his girl or something.
He had like three people in his chat.
And so then, Piranha told her about it
and then Piranha went to his chat
and told him I was an okay person and stuff
and he unbanned me and ever since then he was friendly to me.
And so we'd known each other for a couple of years.
So one night I went in,
I think I paid $35 to mod me
and to dance for me in his underwear, which he did.
And it was a great night.
He deleted that live and stuff.
But here's the, but okay, so a few months ago,
probably three months ago, I made him a song
and I went on his panel and I played the song for him.
He loved it.
And so here's the song.
And this is kind of my memorial video.
And it's just a couple of minutes long.
And I hope you guys enjoy this.
And this is, you can kind of see his personality here.
He also had a cat.
There is his white beater.
If you're bored, you can, um, you can leave, um, whoever's keep saying Goyum and stuff.
But yeah, here's the video and you can leave if you don't want to respect me.
Am I Goyum?
I think he's calling me a Goyum, but here's, here's a Danny, here's a song I made for Danny
Stranger.
I had to put it to like a video after he passed away, but I, this is, I did play the song
for him when he was alive and he loved it.
You can see he's a good looking guy.
Okay.
Then it's stranger walkin' in like a county fair star
Lookin' so cute got that kid rock guitar bar
I'm acting normally and sure okay but my brain's yelling open I made your way
He did one little dance and my soul said fine now I'm losing my dignity one beat at a time
I don't hit him up much I keep it tight cause he's got that charm that can
wreck my night one smile on hate and I'm already sure he'll talk me into something expensive
You're a stranger, you're trouble, you're a cutie tag
I wanna buy your underwear and your socks in a pack
You danced with me once, now I'm down bad facts
But I'm keeping it casual while I'm losing my tracks
And no, he ain't gay, so don't make it weird
I'm just out here spiraling crystal clear
I don't talk to him much cause I know what he'll do
He'll talk me into buying him a whole dang truck
You
He got that I might be problem grand
Like he's selling sunshine with a side of sand
He laughs, I fold my wallet, get scared
I'm tryna play cool, but I'm deeply unprepared
I'm not sayin' I'm obsessed
Just molly the range, like who needs self-respect
When the vibes is strange
I keep my distance, I do my best
But he pops in my head like a bad text
He says we should hang, I'm like maybe soon
My house like a raccoon Danny stranger your trouble your cute attack
I wanna buy your underwear and your socks in a pack you dance for me once now
I'm down bad facts, but I'm keeping it casual. I'm losing my tracks and no we ain't gay
So don't make it weird. I'm just out here spiraling crystal clear
I don't talk to him much cuz I know what I'll do
And I don't even have a buy-goo
I'm a responsible adult allegedly
But that man says,
Babe, in my brain go spend money
I'm not his bank
I'm not his plan
I'm just a humble fan
With a morally questionable stance
If he blinks twice
I'm making poor choices
Hearing cash registers
Like background voices
You're a stranger, you're a trouble, you're a cute attack
I wanna buy your underwear and your socks in a pack
You danced for me once, now I'm down bad facts
But I'm keeping it casual while I'm losing my track
So no, you ain't gay, so don't make it weird
I'm just out here spiraling crystal clear
I don't talk to him that much, cause I know what he'll do
He'll talk me into buying him a whole dang truck
And I don't even have a bike dude
Danny stranger
And I don't even have a bike dude my finances can't take it
And I don't even have a bike dude
I
Somebody's younger
One chip challenge I can play this is on this channel. You mind if I watch
You see the ship is dark
This brave man is also attempting. Now he's not gonna eat all of it. All right. He's not gonna eat all of it
But he is gonna eat a friend. Okay. I was half of it
Yeah
No, he's really cute and he I did like say like
He started charging me five dollars every time I hit on him
And I think by like the second day out of my six hundred dollars and I was like anything
I need a Ford Ranger and I was like well if you if I talk to you for another week
I'm gonna end up buying the Ford Ranger, but I don't have a bike
Even if my bike's broken
Yeah, and that the song was actually
People say I just like make these shit up. I swear
Oh, you want some you want some treats on our I got you and I don't even have a bike dude
That's why it's like it's like true
I don't even like you and then I then I like disappear from his chat that and then he forgot
Joker Joker doesn't like it in the butt. I think Joker is the top
No, it's too painful for me to even poop
No, I mean
It's painful for me, but
I'm not gonna say anything else joker. I can't believe song
It's called the kalimba you ever seen this no, I haven't seen it before it's kind of like a doorbell instrument
that was for you Joker. That's my Joker song.
What do you think Blackout Andy is? Do you think Blackout Andy likes it in the butt?
I think Blackout Andy likes it in the butt. I think he's a queer.
I think, I think he's a queer and do you ever see like Alexander mayors made this hilarious meme
Where it was like it was like blogger and bloggers like doing this is twisted tea stuff
And then it's like blackout Andy in the other room dressed in a nurse's outfit putting drugs in his sandwich
Whoa
That was pretty funny or the super something it was pretty funny
But you know I reconciled with Alexandra. I reconciled with her like I don't I don't know like you know I
think we're like
Headed head in that way, but at least I got to apologize to her and stuff, but yeah
You're gonna do prism. Hey Joker. Do you have a cash app or something?
I want to let my chat know about your cash app or if you have a
You know how I want to but you know what Joker does on his show and I guys
He's what I want and Joker you don't care if there's trolls in your chat
Joker is like you're gonna take her trolls Alice is a good person. I think I
Worry no actually. I know she is but Joker
Okay part where they say but hey
I don't know. I but I want you guys to support. Oh, no. No, here's what I was gonna say
You can go to his chat
And he plays video games and then you can type SR or his exclamation point SR or something exclamation mark or it's just SR
Just exclamation point SR
Explanation point SR and then you can you can say any song you want and he will play your song
It's not he doesn't even he doesn't even charge for I mean it's like but I do recommend like you send him
And I'm gonna send you a little donation soon joker because I like I didn't play my songs and stuff, but
you know, I
Want to support like I don't know if you're are you shadow band or something or you started over
No, I just started over on my channel. Yeah, I get a lot of years. I just I haven't been streaming lately
Yeah, and the first time I saw Joker. I mean I met Joker and Benny's channel right and Benny was I remember the
I remember the night I remember exactly why I met you Joker
Benny was riding his motorbike in like the middle of a forest
And I and then I saw Joker TV call mentioned in the chat and I was like, oh there's somebody with a channel and
So I went and I subscribed to you and then I went to your channel and Joker we went through some ups and downs, didn't we?
Yeah, I didn't know if you were yeah, you were a girl at first, right and then I
Remember clumsy came on like one of the first episodes and you're and you're like and then I said I like Mexican guys
And you're I don't know if this guy's psyche is like a man or a woman or whatever
But I think he's hitting on you clumsy
I was like what the fuck what the fuck what what's going on and then I remember I met Bita on your channel
I met Nick Johnson. He was Erica Bob do you he just took over your channel one night. It was it was Erica Bob do I
Know I know I'm not anymore. I meant who else that I mean I meant I just met so many people on your channel
And then what did you say? What did you tell me just one night?
Then you then you were like and I was hitting on you in the channel and stuff
and you said,
Psychi, I'm about to ban you
because you're being weird and stuff.
And you didn't ban me, but you almost did.
You might've timed me out or something,
but you didn't ban-
No, I didn't know, I didn't know.
I know, it's okay, it's okay.
Guys, I've been banned by a lot of people, it's okay.
Cause I'm, you know,
most people are like square people, they're squares.
And I'm kind of like,
Not a square person, you know, I'm like I'm like a I'm like a what is it called a hexagram or a
What's the what's the chat? I'm a trapezoid basically. I'm like a triangle with the tip with the tip cut off
I don't know what I am but
I'm kind of weird and then I remember your Indian friend and you you had an Indian friend over and I was like
Can you guys flex for me and you and your Indian friend give me a flex show in the backyard? You remember that night?
Yeah, I remember that I was when I was yeah, I was not doing I was on Joker channel is mr. X dendo
It's mr. X letter X is it X ten do mr. X ten do
Is that it yeah, I'm just trying to do two things at once. I'm
Yeah, I don't
I'm sorry. I'm having trouble like you know, exactly
I don't I don't care what Joker is. Here's what I care about. I don't care about Joker's in a sexual way
I just care that Joker was always
What did you say to me Joker you said hey psych
Because I was like I want to be a steamer
As I don't want to be I was I was positive towards psych when I was like, you know
You should definitely try to stream me
You should try doing a podcast because I can see you doing it because you have like you're in the chat and you have all these
questions and you know
You know what it takes to do it so you can do it and so he started doing it and now he has a
3000 subscriber channel when he got around 2000 subscribers. That's when you had the most problems
I know hey page page
You know Paige remember Paige Joker you do the you do the drawing of her with a big long neck
Hey, come on up
It's a had a bit
Joker I
Don't know if you talk to Joe. Let me look at a version of I gotta draw a page. I gotta see yeah
I gotta draw again. You draw another French page is your French woman a French Canadian woman. I think it's called
I'm gonna draw a cartoon woman
Let's do it. Hey, hey, you come up so Joker can get a better
Look and maybe we can do a car for car for a few if he's down for it
I'll do a car for card with Joker
Remember the Joker and Alice era. I remember Alice came in my chat or as a shadow pages anime
Yeah, do well do however you want to do it. Just just however you whatever your heart with a Joker
What are you guys the anime or no anime do I say anime, but whatever she says, but Joker here's a good thing about Joker
He has a really good heart. He really does he could have said I thought he I thought he was maybe homophobic and stuff
He's running around on a skateboard. He pulled like money out of a sock. I remember he was in the
Remember when you were in the middle of I know
Then we all have our tweaker days, right? We are you thought that I was on I was definitely tweaked out. Yeah
Yeah
Okay, well, it's okay Paige
I'll be on a skateboard and stream and do a bunch of goofy stuff
Yeah, but I remember you had like skin knees and you know that your knees your skin and you like pulled money of your sock
You're like, hey, I'm like five minutes down the middle of some road and some forest and stuff
So I was hanging out with my friend who was a alleged drug dealer, right and we were walking on the road
Then all of a sudden all these undercover cars started chasing us around and there were cops
And they chase remember the woods they chased us into the woods
And I fell down in the woods and I distracted the cops on my other friend ran away and
Then I had to walk through the woods by myself. I was there. I was getting super hot. It was like a hundred and one degrees outside
Did you remember I was there Joker? No, do you remember that I was there in the chat today, and I was sitting under the bridge
Yeah, and I was having a good time wasn't I I was having a good time too and I was like
It was and I was like I was like this guy's funny as fuck because it was like his and that time Benny had just been inside and stuff
And then you were or he was did the motorist motorbike stuff, but you were like out in a skateboard or the stuff
You know the sound about yeah, you're out about living the city anymore
Now I live in the middle of the woods and you were like there a car would drive by and you're like
This car's following me. I saw this car like three times go back and forth. That's because I had I had
PTSD because last time there was a bunch of unmarked cars following my friend, right?
You're like, I'm going to hang out with them. I remember that I went to hang out with them, right?
And it was actually cops. They were like DEA cops trying to bust them and they were following me because I hung out with him, you see
So then I thought that they were following me around and they kept following me around to see if I would go hang out with them
Because they're following him first, but then whenever he hung out with me, he lost him
So he called them he called me to hang out with them to lose the cops basically
Right, and I remember that and someone's saying I attract the young gays. No Joker grew me Benny grew me
These guys told me what to do. I didn't tell them what to do. They told me what to do
Someone said coming funny on funny. They're like if you were to be Benny Blanco in person
Psyche he would beat you up and steal your wallet
And I do believe that and I don't know if you would too a someone and Maya Maya posted your channel by the way
Yeah, that's my channel. Mr. Extendo. That's what I show you with the W at the end, right?
Yeah, with the W but Joker and
Joker did I ever make you like and I'm sorry if I did and you can answer honestly
Did I was like too over the top with my sexual jokes and then I make you uncomfortable and like it felt weird
No
You're your first guys and Joker's honest as fuck. He didn't really hesitate or anything like I really everything made me so scared
I was so scared of you. Ah, I know and you're only like two thousand miles away
I did you invite you to move in with me and stuff and share my bed, but that was funny, right? And you almost said yes, but
Guys it's called jokes. It's called
Trying to be funny and stuff
I'm a voodoo ranger. I'm on my number four. I'm not a voodoo. I have no voodoo rangers
I'm on my last. I think pink lemonade. Do I have another pink lemonade?
Not there. Oh, I do. I have another. I have one more left. I have an ice-mashed peach mango
But I'm pretty drunk. I'm pretty fucking drunk right now. So I don't know if I'll get there. It's only 11 p.m
Here come the birds tar later take the liver maybe an eyeball. So here's what I found one night. Okay, so
I've seen coyotes, like I remember when my cat,
I had kittens and the kittens were outside
and I saw a coyote walking around outside
and I was so fucking scared for the kittens.
This is when I lived in Glendale,
but the kittens were hiding me in the bush.
And then a few like days later,
I saw a, it was a baby red-tailed hawk,
a baby was like sitting on the path.
Also, I saved a squirrel's life.
There was a squirrel.
I don't know how he got injured or something,
but the squirrel was at the bottom of the tree,
like as a baby squirrel.
laying at the bottom of the street and I like drove two hours to some wildlife rescue to like
save this baby's squirrel and stuff when I lived in Glendale and so but I don't know I saw I really
believe in animal omens joker tell me about your favorite animal omens uh
Omen's from animals.
Well, I mean, it's okay.
So like, for example, my friend, her brother passed away
and then she saw dragonflies.
And my grandma passed away.
I saw butterflies.
Her whole, my grandma, I saw hummingbirds actually.
My grandfather, I saw butterflies.
And if I walk past the tree,
okay, I'm gonna call for Trixie right now.
I'm gonna turn off my microphone so I don't wanna like,
but yeah, so I believe in animal omens
and I believe Trixie will come back.
I'll be right back.
Tracey sometimes
Yeah, he's sometimes
Go away from what I'm gonna go call from a perfect my bag. Yeah, I'm gonna shake the bag. Yeah, I've been watching ear wax removal videos
It's not nasty
Watching this guy gets here
Think I want to be a ear doctor when I grow up
So I do see how firm I shook the bag.
So earwax removal videos.
These can be good.
You ever see like a huge chunk of earwax being removed?
Like a disgustingly large.
They're disgustingly satisfying to watch occasionally.
I've also seen pimple popping videos,
where they're like, oh, I have a pimple.
And it's like, it just like shoots out, it's disgusting.
I don't know how people will let their ear get so impacted before they go to the doctor. Oh my god
It's like giant balls of like like an inch thick in your ear. Okay. Well, I mean, I'm probably gonna like I want to show you
Something that will make some people scream and stuff like that and I'm gonna end the stream after because it's probably copyrighted
This was on ever go hunting. Yeah, sorry. Did they ask me a question?
Shepherds like I'm gonna find this video but
Yeah, I've been hunting. I also go fishing a lot. I got two fishing poles that I got and
They're really nice like
$300 a piece and they're a really nice fishing poles for bass and I put rooster tails
On a rooster tail hooks, so I've been fishing with rooster tails and that's how I've been catching a lot of fish
rooster tails
Yeah, I'll drive deer if my period is in the hunt season. I got you
Yeah, there's deer all over the place where I live. There's deer everywhere every time I go outside
There's deer. I live in the middle of nowhere in Georgia in between
making and
Atlanta and there's nothing there's nothing but farms and little tiny small towns
But now they're starting to build all these like bougie
Mansions on land selling parcels of land and so it's like it's like not really like suburbs. It's like country
Everything is on septic. So there's no like
It's in the country, you know
We're doing small towns. There's no McDonald's or Burger King's anywhere
The closest store I have is a dollar general
Yeah, there's nothing. There's nothing
Yeah, I
Mean I'm gonna find now I have developed a southern accent
And you're in the South you're like South Carolina or I don't want to say exactly but you're in the South
Okay, I'll do it. You're in Georgia
Hey
Georgia
A Georgia on my mind. I mean that song
Yeah, that's wrong. You heard of it. Yeah, I figured if you're in Georgia, you heard of it
But um, okay, I can't find the there's like the worst episode of my feet are killing me. There's kind of like a southern guy
And he has like such bad feet. They have to like use a sandblaster on them and like
It is crazy. I just I don't believe it's not showing up right now
I'm gonna go and usually look for it one second
But yeah, I'm gonna find it and then if I find it then I'm gonna play it and then I'm gonna restart the stream
because I don't want to get struck but
You just guys have to see this. I mean you have I mean if you like if you don't like gross things
I'm sorry, but
Some things are like, you know, I just think I think it's somebody with a terrible foot problem like this guy had and
How the doctors are able to help him and then
And so there's a beautiful I just a beautiful thing I
My feet are killing me. Okay. I
Think it should be like the top video for it, but I don't know why it's not
These are about podiatrists. My best friend in high school was like
her dad was a podiatrist and
You know, they lived they made bank and he or he made bank, right?
And oh my god, someone. This is a really too disturbing to look at
Maybe I won't play any of this. I mean, it's really disgusting. So I probably okay. Never never mind
I just saw something that made me
Want to cry and so never mind never mind never mind
I'm not gonna show it, but yeah guys go watch my feet are killing me. You're gonna see some fucking crazy shit
Did I find tricks? No, but I've called for him
I've woken up often with him sitting right there often
He comes running up the stairs
I
Hope it's okay. The only thing I'm worried about if he like at the end of the day
He's like, he's the cutest cat and stuff and he'll be fine. Like if he's okay
The only thing I'm worried about is like if he's not okay. That's part of the thing of having outdoor cats is
Like you got to just have like, you know, let him go out when they want to let him come back when they want to
I'm I'm 90% sure he'll come back
Yeah, but um, like then 95% actually if he's fine, I'm a hundred percent sure I'll find him
A car or something like that. That's not a worry about but I don't think he's like the type
That would go in the street or cry across the street
But guys imagine if your parents too and your parents sending your kid out to he's been gone this long
He's been gone for 24 hours before
Yeah, he's been gone for this long before and he always comes back
Ever call once again. I'm Rebecca's good. Oh, sorry. I'm Rebecca. I'm Joker. Can you talk to the chat for a second? I'll be back
Yeah, what's up everybody I'm just trying to set up my my stream on my phone so I'm doing
I'm just trying to figure out how to get it to work
I want to see if the microphone issue is just on the YouTube app or if it's all apps and
It looks like it was just with the YouTube app
Microphone microphone
Microphone
Yeah, my mic's working it's working good actually
I do not talk to dope district
How do you not talk to any of the streamer people none of them were real friends just the thing that that's the problem with it
At least psych is the night's friend and you don't have to worry about like some utter betrayal with all those
Streamers that I stream with from the IPT community. They're all are down to try to portray you as soon as you get more viewers than them
Outdoor cats, I have outdoor cats and they decided to like live outdoors and they never came back
So guys we have a borrow
Hey guys
Ghosts go guys should be quiet but ghost
Met a woman and he's gonna come up with it right now
Okay, you know my friend goes he met he met someone special
He met a woman
He asked me for permission to crash out and he said can I bring my my female friend over I just met her
guys
Let's support it goes. Oh boy. Are you there? Oh?
Yeah, I like Mike
There he is
I'm a big fan of jokers
You are
What about me? What about me? I'm just top liver
Yeah
Okay, okay
Joker you have a fan
I, I, I don't have any fans, but joker. I love joker. I love joker too. Joker.
Good guy. Joker, Joker, have you heard of Lucky Pierre, Joker? Have you heard of Lucky Pierre?
No, I haven't.
Lucky Pierre is the guy in the middle. He's fucking somebody in the ass, and he's getting fucked in the ass
Right
I'm doing it lucky. I'm doing it. I've lost our with a bar
Switched it to
Other side
There we go. Oh my god high five high five Alvaro, how does it feel?
Not good
But you in the middle site, okay, can I be in the middle now? I want to be the lucky pier
of our long
Hey, I saw you on Kate's the other day and you were showing you're a fucking the
American underwear or whatever the fuck that was my American underwear. Yeah, you know what the fuck it reminded me of what?
Shannon
And her bony bow get out of here. Get out your bad push up. No, I'm just kidding. Why you know Shanna is missing a leg
Yeah, but it's she's bony, bro. It reminded me of that. She like you were so you're so bony
Hey, you I'm balding. I don't say balding. I said bony. Oh bony. Okay. I'll be right back
I want you and Joker to talk for me. I have to be
I already know Joker man. That's who fucking gay as fuck
You don't like gay people. Don't go joking gay. If you if you make fun of my boyfriend, I'm gonna hit you with my purse
Okay
I'm not gay though
What you fucking that black fool what the fuck was that black fool's name your friend or Khalil?
I didn't I didn't fuck anybody. They got fucked. He got fucked
Didn't mean do I
Just stuck it in them on accident
Both of them had female butts. I couldn't figure out which one. How did you meet Khalil?
He was a cross-dresser on the side of the road. No, no, how'd you meet him, bro?
That's how I met him. No, no for real. How'd you meet him? I?
Was looking for a cross-dresser
How'd you ever meet him for it was online?
It was no I met him through
He's a cross-sister
Joker alone leave Joker alone Joker is yeah a guy
Alvaro female butt. It was a man with a female butt Joker. You owe me
Your butt Alvaro
Thank you
No, thank you. Okay. At least you were polite about it. Okay
Okay, okay. Have you ever seen the man with the giant BBL?
Sam yeah
Oh, he's the worst isn't he the absolute worst person in the world I I mean, I swear, I'm not kidding. He's like
He's the worst
Sam answer words, but they got a bbl. Let me think yeah, you know, I really hope
It's bigger than that way bigger
You need to eat, bro
You need some more carne open that shit
Can I get you with your front end sawed up in me?
I ain't gonna put no carne sawed up in you, bro
But that shit needs no carne
For there ain't no carne
It's no tipo hueso
Hueso? How about some carnejo?
Can I put a bit dejo in me?
A bit dejo
Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay.
Hello. Hello. Hello. I
Am
Okay, I'm setting up
Look at other sims staying quiet when he says woman including me and Joker
I know we're all surprised. Okay, guys. We're all surprised
Call you a joker if you don't mind
Call me. I'm a cult member now. Call me cold
It's calm cultists
Phillip Coles is joker
Ali, what is it? Yeah, is she in the back? No, not yet. I was guessing
Oh, never mind. Okay. Oh, you know. Oh, it was Carla. I guess it right the first time
I
Did guys that's why I'm called a psychic I guess
She's actually charging her headphones. Okay. I'll be right back
I'll be right. I'm gonna wait for Carla to get here and then I'll let her up and I'll come back out
You guys talk like bros, okay?
What's so other like
Do you feel comfortable with your foreskin?
There's supposed to be another winter storm coming up.
What did you say?
There's this guy who I think is a serial killer.
I'm in a regiment for reenacting Civil War games and like the Pollyanna games.
And there's a guy in my regiment and he always asks this question.
I think he's a serial killer.
and he says are you comfortable in your skin are you comfortable in your skin are you comfortable in your skin are you comfortable in your skin are you comfortable in your skin are you comfortable in your skin are you comfortable in your skin are you comfortable in your skin are you comfortable in your skin are you comfortable in your skin are you comfortable in your skin are you comfortable in your skin are you comfortable in your skin are you comfortable in your skin are you comfortable in your skin are you comfortable in your skin are you comfortable in your skin are you comfortable in your skin are you comfortable in your skin are you comfortable in your skin are you comfortable in your skin are you comfortable in your skin are you comfortable in your skin are you comfortable in your skin are you comfortable in your skin are you comfortable in your skin are you comfortable in your skin are you comfortable in your skin are you comfortable in your skin are you comfortable in your skin are you comfortable in your skin are you comfortable in your skin are you comfortable in your skin are you comfortable in your skin are you comfortable in your skin are you comfortable in your skin are you comfortable in
No, I don't know who that is
You can give to the membership or you a natural subscriber. I'm just a natural subscriber
Are you what is your fan of mine? I don't know I just I
Come by your show every now and then are you seeing on a wish changer?
No, no, not at all. Are you the guy that showed his ballsack on beat is the other night
No, I'm the guy that comes up here every now and then drops the n-bomb. So that's what I
Okay, you're gone
He just said he drops it. I mean he was on funny man. I like is he gay. That's the question you should have asked him off
I don't think subscriber. I don't think I remember a Zach Baggins in the channel. I don't remember a Zach Baggins a subscriber
Uh-oh, ghost dropped off ghost. I want to meet Camille very soon. Okay?
Alvaro, have you ever had a gay experience? Yes, tell me about it. I
Got raped and I had to
Out of here
I'm sorry, you may answer that question so I got
Tell me so I got
He please tell me please tell me Joker. I want to hear it. I don't want to hear about
No, no, I don't have any answer to that question. No, you said what happened with Khalil that night
Well, he was a cross-dresser, so he was and you guys didn't put it in his butt
Accidentally, yeah, okay
And one of the guys I know it's confusing when you woke up and was it Khalil giving you a blowjob that night or is another guy
No, it was a guy. I know and no, no, I was it wasn't Khalil was another guy. Okay
No, it was him. It was okay. It was clear and did you finish in his mouth? He said his name is Kalisha
Okay, hey puppy who says abs puppy who was his accidents happen
Yeah
Again, I want to ask you what happened with clumsy though. Why were you hitting it like after me and you were together?
I never I never never hit on clumsy
I have the video actually I don't know that is not it that video is out of context
I don't I don't think it is I don't think it is and I want to play the video
It's like it is past my bedtime. Oh, hey. Oh my oh now you have to go. Hey, we have a guest though
Just talk to the guests for a minute
What is puppy woo woo? Oh?
puppy woo woo
You're a nigger
What did you say to me? I said that
He said he likes vinegar. He said vinegar. I heard. I just heard vinegar vinegar. Yeah
Did everyone else here vinegar I said I heard I heard vinegar
Here's what I'm gonna say to you Joker. I'm sorry you're good sport. I know it wasn't even bears you Joker
I had a I went on a day with a black guy. I had never had anal and he kind of like
Was like, okay, let's do this the way and I was like no and then all of a sudden it just happened
And so I understand the accidents happen
Accidents happen
Yeah, I wasn't the same as yours. I know it wasn't but I'm just saying I have an understanding and Joker
You know you're my friend and Joker if you ever need it was the opposite of yours. It was the opposite
Yeah, and I know you if you're receiving anal you were giving him
Yeah, you were giving it. Okay, but I just want to say Joker
I was I was I was just presenting my sword and they put their sword in their bus
Alvaro, what do you think of that Alvaro?
What are you gonna be don't but don't say anything gross or anything wrong I never said anything
We're gross or wrong
But I want to say good night to Joker and I want to say good night Joker. You know you're my friend
I love Joker long Joker for like five years. I love Joker. Okay, and I'm no Joker for two years and stuff
You know what this guy's awesome. Everyone's subscribed to mr. Extendo w
Jamie Cowboys is here. I'm too spated for this right now
From a big homo to a straight guy. No
Okay, bye bye my I'm not alone on the panel am I oh my dear God
What just happened? Hey, we have a guest tonight all the way from Canada
He's a warlock. He has mind control abilities. He might just be in love with beta and sweepy. I'm still figuring that part out
You guys know who it is
He's the thing
He might be the one that is
Let's welcome
Hello, you're a gay n***
Wow
Thing that is I thought you're my friend why would you say that to me thing that is I?
Trusted you I trusted you on my show
Thing that is I thought you're my friend
Why would you say such a thing?
That was terrible
Thing that is why?
You're laughing about it. Why are you laughing?
Raise the rain I see you there. I don't want to hear the n-word again
I'm gonna end the stream and restart it and delete the last one so I don't get you know hate speech
Okay, join my new stream. Okay a razor rain come right back. Okay. I love you